<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<root> 
  <data id="0" primaryimagepath="/theme/images/home-natural.jpg"
  primaryimagepathwide="/theme/images/home-natural-wide.jpg" 
  >
  <caption><![CDATA[Projects to support, renew and celebrate the environment]]></caption>
    <name> 
      <language id="en"><![CDATA[Sol Vida Dynamico]]></language> 
    </name> 
    <summary>The natural world is a treasure that sustains all life, brings harmony to our ecosystems, and nourishes our souls. Its abundance nurtures our well-being, offering solace, inspiration, and a deep connection to the world around us.  However, our natural world is in danger right now from threats like pollution and industrialization.  By embracing and protecting this remarkable gift , we ensure a thriving future filled with endless possibilities.
    </summary>
  </data>  
  <data id="1"  primaryimagepath="/theme/images/home-creative.jpg"
  primaryimagepathwide="/theme/images/home-creative-wide.jpg"
  >
    <caption><![CDATA[The Arts, Music and Performance]]></caption>
    <name> 
      <language id="en"><![CDATA[Common Roots Collective]]></language> 
    </name> 
    <summary>
    Artists everywhere need our help to create thriving communities and events!  The arts provide connect people across cultures and generations. By nurturing creativity, we are able to cultivate innovative thinking, problem-solving skills, and emotional intelligence. Let us embrace the power of creativity and invest in the the arts.  The arts are a way to celebrate our shared humanity and promote understanding in our diverse world.
    </summary>
  </data>  
  <data id="2"  primaryimagepath="/theme/images/home-human.jpg"
  primaryimagepathwide="/theme/images/home-human-wide.jpg">
    <name> 
      <language id="en"><![CDATA[Kansha Academy]]></language> 
    </name> 
    <caption><![CDATA[Education, health, assistance and cultural preservation]]></caption>
    
    <summary>
    Many people around the world don't have access to basic human needs. Together, we can create a world where every person has access to the resources they need to thrive.  Charities and organizations worldwide are working tirelessly to ensure that basic needs such as food security, shelter, health, and education are met for everyone. With the help of technological advancements, we can take this progress even further.    
    </summary>
  </data>
  <data id="3"  primaryimagepath="/theme/images/home-technology.jpg"
  primaryimagepathwide="/theme/images/home-technology-wide.jpg"
  > 
    <name> 
      <language id="en"><![CDATA[eMedia]]></language> 
    </name>
    <caption><![CDATA[Software, tools, science in the common wellness]]></caption>
    
    <summary>
    Open technology is one of the most important advancements in humanity. It has brought efficiency, new jobs, and advancements that have made our lives better. This resource has allowed for collaboration and innovation on a scale never before seen. With open technology, we have access to tools that can help us solve some of the world's biggest problems. From renewable energy to healthcare.
    
    </summary>
   
  </data>    
  <data id="4" logo="/theme/images/logos/tierrasagrada.svg" primaryimagepath="/theme/images/home-technology.jpg" externaldomain="tierrasagrada.openinstitute.org:8080"
  primaryimagepathwide="/theme/images/home-technology-wide.jpg"
  domaincommunityid="4"
  > 
    <name> 
      <language id="en"><![CDATA[Tierra Sagrada]]></language> 
    </name>
    <caption><![CDATA[Rentals that give back to the local community]]></caption>
    
    <summary>
    <![CDATA[
    An collaborative booking platform that focuses on giving back to and empowering communities around Lake Atitlan. 5% of profits goes to projects that are conserving land, educating children, supporting musicians, and having a positive social and justice impact.
    ]]>
    </summary>
   
  </data>    
</root>
